imp3king.com 2018-11-19

# Privacy | Imp3king.com

## Personal Information

Imp3king.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our web site. In order to enhance your experience at our sites we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, zip code, and country. The more information you share with us (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to enhance and customize your experience on our sites. 

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Imp3king.com as outlined in this privacy policy. Imp3king.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third party unless specified.

## IP address and logging

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Imp3king.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. For more information about Google.com, cookies, how to "opt-out", and all other privacy policies please visit google.com/adsense/terms.

## Cookies

Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
